Center for Environmental Management Records UA096
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Publications, 1985 -- 1994; UA096.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Series includes CEM and non-CEM publications. CEM publications include the CEM newsletter called "CEM Report," as well as the Talloires University Group publications, and research reports from CEM-funded investigators. Non-CEM publications include reports of research related to those conducted by CEM-sponsored researchers, and a few newsletters published by partner organizations.
  This series is arranged by personal or institutional author.
  - Brown, H.J., The Transition to a Regenerative Resource Economy, 1992; UA096.004.016.00019 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Animals and Public Policy, The Alternative Report, 1989; UA096.004.016.00020 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Environmental Management, Asbestos Information Center, 1985; UA096.004.016.00021 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Environmental Management, Brochures, 1988 -- 1993; UA096.004.016.00022 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Environmental Management, CEM Report, 1991 -- 1994; UA096.004.016.00023 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Environmental Management, Handbook for Preparing Assurance Plans for Environmental Measures, 1989; UA096.004.016.00024 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Center for Environmental Management, State and Provincial Responses to Global Climte Change, 1990; UA096.004.016.00025 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Chabot, A., Initivatives in Environmental Education, 1993; UA096.004.016.00026 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Craig, A.C., et al., Prevalence of Leukemia in Hemolymph of Soft-Shell Clams, 1989; UA096.004.016.00027 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Creighton, S.H., Solid Waste Reduction in Colleges and Universities: A Status Report, 1993; UA096.004.016.00028 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Education for Public Inquiry and International Citizenship, Confronting Political and Social Evil, 1991; UA096.004.016.00029 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Flaherty, M., Multinational Corporations and the Environment: A Survey of Global Practices, 1991; UA096.004.016.00030 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Jacobson, S., In Utero Effects of Trichloroethylene, UA096.004.016.00031 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Leavitt, D. F., et al., Hemotopoietic neoplasia in Mya arenaria, 1986; UA096.004.016.00032 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Levine, S. H., et al., Pest Management Through Habitat Design, 1991; UA096.004.016.00033 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - McNamara, R., A Vision For Our Nation and the World in the 21st Century, 1991; UA096.004.016.00034 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Moomaw, W. R., A Northeast Response to Global Climate Change, 1991; UA096.004.016.00035 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Snyder, R., An Action Plan for the Protection of the Saugus River, 1991; UA096.004.016.00036 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
- Conferences and Seminars, 1985 -- 1991; UA096.005; 1.95 Linear Feet
  This series consists of files describing conferences organized or co-organized by CEM between 1985 and 1991, including The Greening of Industry conference, conferences for Household Hazardous Waste Management, as well as multiple conferences focusing on waste reduction. This series also includes information on the seminars offered in conjunction with the Talloires program.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Waste Reduction - The Untold Story June 19-21, 1985; UA096.005.016.00037 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Waste Reduction - The Ongoing Saga June 4-6, 1986; UA096.005.016.00038 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Summary of the First National Conference on Household Hazardous Waste Collection Programs November 18-20, 1986; UA096.005.016.00039 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Forum Concerning the Establishment of a Clearinghouse for CERCLA/RCRA Cleanup Technologies April 22-23, 1987; UA096.005.016.00040 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Managing Environmental Risk in Newly Industrializing Countries May 10-14, 1987; UA096.005.016.00041 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Waste Reduction - The Hurdles Ahead June 3-5, 1987; UA096.005.016.00042 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Waste Minimization Policy Forum July 13-15, 1987; UA096.005.016.00043 (Box UA096 Shared 1)
  - Summary of the Second National Conference on Household Hazardous Waste Management November 2-4, 1987; UA096.005.017.00001 (Box 17)
  - Conference Summary: Municipal Solid Waste Source Reduction and Recycling Conference March 23-25, 1988; UA096.005.017.00002 (Box 17)
  - Conference Summary: Waste Reduction - A Cooperative Search for Solution June 15-17, 1988; UA096.005.017.00003 (Box 17)
  - Waste Reduction - A Cooperative Search for Solution June 15-17, 1988; UA096.005.017.00004 (Box 17)
  - Summary of the Third National Conference on Household Hazardous Waste Management November 2-4, 1988; UA096.005.017.00005 (Box 17)
  - The Talloires University Group Newsletter February, 1989; UA096.005.018.00001 (Box 18)
  - Reshaping Institutions to Meet Environmental Crises: Beyond Business as Usual May 14-18, 1989; UA096.005.018.00002 (Box 18)
  - A Report on the Forum - Environmental Risk Communication: Lessons Learned April, 1990; UA096.005.018.00003 (Box 18)
  - Report and Declaration of the Presidents Conference October 4-7, 1990; UA096.005.018.00004 (Box 18)
  - Technological Cooperation for Sustainable Development May 6-9, 1991; UA096.005.018.00005 (Box 18)
  - The Greening of Industry International Research Conference November, 1991; UA096.005.018.00006 (Box 18)
- Additional accessions, 1988-1995; UA096.006
  - Publications and binders, 1990 -- 1995; UA096-001 (Box data_value_missing_09e22e437bac8633d2022465a455ffa5, Box 1)
  - Slides, photos and clippings, 1988 -- 1995; UA096-002 (Box data_value_missing_09e22e437bac8633d2022465a455ffa5, Box 2)
  - Slides and photos, 1988 -- 1995; UA096-003 (Box data_value_missing_09e22e437bac8633d2022465a455ffa5, Box 3)
  - HRI Documents Box 1, 1990; UA096-020 (Box data_value_missing_c24376006b78309d4451ce5662495b2c, Box 4)
  - HRI Documents Box 2, 1990; UA096-021 (Box data_value_missing_c24376006b78309d4451ce5662495b2c, Box 5)
  - HRI Documents Box 3, 1990; UA096-022 (Box data_value_missing_c24376006b78309d4451ce5662495b2c, Box 6)